IT'S ALL BASED OFF OF LOVE, AND
LOVE ISN'T DO THIS FOR ME
AND I'M GONNA DO THIS FOR YOU
THAT'S NOT WHAT LOVE IS.
LOVE IS JUST I'M GONNA DO
THIS FOR YOU BECAUSE
I WANT TO DO THIS FOR YOU.
♪ FOR ALL THE TIMES THAT YOU
RAINED ON MY PARADE ♪
♪ AND ALL THE CLUBS YOU GET IN
USING MY NAME ♪
♪ YOU THINK YOU BROKE MY HEART,
OH GIRL FOR GOODNESS SAKE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'M CRYING ON MY
OWN, WELL I AIN'T ♪
♪ AND I DIDN'T WANT TO
WRITE A SONG ♪
♪ CAUSE DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
THINKING I STILL CARE, I DON'T ♪
♪ BUT, YOU STILL HIT MY
PHONE UP ♪
♪ AND BABY ILL BE MOVING ON ♪
♪ AND I THINK IT SHOULD BE
SOMETHING I DON'T WANT TO ♪
♪ HOLD BACK, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD KNOW THAT ♪
♪ MY MOMMA DON'T LIKE YOU, AND
SHE LIKES EVERYONE ♪
♪ AND I NEVER LIKE TO ADMIT
THAT I WAS WRONG ♪
♪ AND I'VE BEEN SO CAUGHT UP IN
MY JOB, DIDN'T SEE ♪
♪ WHAT'S GOING ON AND
NOW I KNOW ♪
♪ I'M BETTER SLEEPING
ON MY OWN ♪
♪ CAUSE IF YOU LIKE THE WAY YOU
LOOK THAT MUCH, OH BABY ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THINK THAT I'M
STILL HOLDING ON TO SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ BUT WHEN YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU
HATED MY FRIENDS ♪
♪ THE ONLY PROBLEM WAS WITH YOU
AND NOT THEM ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME YOU TOLD ME MY
OPINION WAS WRONG ♪
♪ AND TRIED TO MAKE ME FORGET
WHERE I CAME FROM ♪
♪ AND I DIDN'T WANT TO
WRITE A SONG ♪
♪ CAUSE DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
THINKING I STILL CARE, I DON'T ♪
♪ BUT YOU STILL HIT MY
PHONE UP ♪
♪ AND BABY ILL BE MOVING ON ♪
♪ AND I THINK IT SHOULD BE
SOMETHING THAT I DON'T WANT TO ♪
♪ HOLD BACK, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD KNOW THAT ♪
♪ MY MOMMA DON'T LIKE YOU,
AND SHE LIKES EVERYONE ♪
♪ AND I NEVER LIKE TO ADMIT
THAT I WAS WRONG ♪
♪ AND I'VE BEEN SO CAUGHT UP IN
MY JOB ♪
♪ DIDN'T SEE WHAT'S GOING
ON AND NOW I KNOW ♪
♪ I'M BETTER SLEEPING
ON MY OWN ♪
♪ CAUSE IF YOU LIKE THE WAY YOU
LOOK THAT MUCH, OH BABY ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THINK THAT I'M
STILL HOLDING ON TO SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ ♪
♪ FOR ALL THE TIMES THAT YOU
MADE ME FEEL SMALL ♪
♪ I FELL IN LOVE, NOW I FEEL
NOTHING AT ALL ♪
♪ I NEVER FELT SO LOW WHEN
I WAS VULNERABLE ♪
♪ WAS I FOOL TO LET YOU
BREAK DOWN MY WALLS? ♪
♪ CAUSE IF YOU LIKE THE WAY YOU
LOOK THAT MUCH, OH BABY ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THINK THAT I'M
STILL HOLDING ON TO SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ CAUSE IF YOU LIKE THE WAY YOU
LOOK THAT MUCH, OH BABY ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THINK (YOU THINK)
THAT I'M (THAT I'M) ♪
♪ STILL HOLDING ON
TO SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD GO AND
LOVE YOURSELF ♪